Guide to The Polytechnic Reporter RG.025
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series I: Loose newspapers
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1926 December 15 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 January 5 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 January 12 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 February 9 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 February 16 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 February 23 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 16 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 23 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 March 30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 April 6 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 April 13 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 May 4 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 May 11 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1927 May 18 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1941 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1941 June 11 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1941 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 April 10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 May 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 September 11 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 September 25 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 16 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 24 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 October 31 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 6 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 November 26 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 4 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 4 (Special Issue) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1975 December 19 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 January 30 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 February 6 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 February 27 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 4 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 12 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 18 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 March 25 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 9 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 23 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 April 30 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Fall 1976 (Special Registration Issue), 1976 Fall (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 September 24 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 8 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 22 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 October 29 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 November 5 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 November 12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 December 16 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 December 23 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Status of the Polytechnic Reporter, 1976 December (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 January 28 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 February 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 February 18 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 4 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 11 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 18 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 March 25 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pyrotepnic Reporter, 1977 April 0? (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 April 7 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 April 22 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 April 29 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 May 6 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 September 16 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 September 30 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 14 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 21 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 October 28 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 4 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 11 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 18 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 November 23 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 9 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 16 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1977 December 23 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 3 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 10 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 17 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 February 24 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 10 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 17 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 March 23 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 7 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 14 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 April 27 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 May 5 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 September 15 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 September 22 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 September 29 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 October 6 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 October 13 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, 1978 October 20 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Polytechnic Reporter, 1994 February 9
  - Polytechnic Reporter, 2003 April 23
  - Polytechnic Reporter, 2003 September 17
- Series II: Bound newspapers
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 6, No. 1-29 (bound), 1918-1919 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 1)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 7, No. 1-26 (bound), 1919-1920 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 2)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 8, No. 1-28 (bound), 1920-1921 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 3)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 9, No. 1-29 (bound), 1921-1922 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 4)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 11 (bound), 1923-1924 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 5)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 12 (bound), 1924-1925 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 6)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 14, No. 1-27 (bound), 1926-1927 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 7)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 15 (bound), 1927-1928 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 8)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 16 (bound), 1928-1929 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 9)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 17 (bound), 1929-1930 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 10)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 18 (bound), 1930-1931 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 11)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 19 (bound), 1931-1932 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 12)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 20 (bound), 1932-1933 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 13)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 21 (bound), 1933-1934 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 14)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 22 (bound), 1934-1935 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 15)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 23 (bound), 1935-1936 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 16)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 24 (bound), 1936-1937 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 17)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 25 (bound), 1937-1938 (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 18)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 26 (bound), 1938-1939 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 19)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 30 (bound), 1939-1940 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 20)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 31 (bound), 1940-1941 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 21)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 32 (bound), 1941-1942 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 22)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 33 (bound), 1942-1943 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 23)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 35-39 (bound), 1944-1946 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 24)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 40 (bound), 1947-1948 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 25)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 41 (bound), 1948-1949 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 26)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 43 (bound), 1950-1951 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 27)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 46 (bound), 1953-1954 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 28)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 47 (bound), 1954-1955 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 29)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 48 (bound), 1955-1956 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 30)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 50 (bound), 1957-1958 (Item Shelf 36/6E, Volume 31)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 51 (bound), 1958-1959 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 32)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 52 (bound), 1959-1960 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 33)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 53 (bound), 1960-1961 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 34)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 54 (bound), 1961-1962 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 35)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 55 (bound), 1962-1963 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 36)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 56 (bound), 1963-1964 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 37)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 57 (bound), 1964-1965 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 38)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 58 (bound), 1965-1966 (Item Shelf 36/2F, Volume 39)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 59 (bound), 1966-1967 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 40)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 60 (bound), 1967-1968 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 41)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 61 (bound), 1968-1969 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 42)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 62 (bound), 1969-1970 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 43)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 63 (bound), 1970-1971 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 44)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 64 (bound), 1971-1972 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 45)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 65 (bound), 1972-1973 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 46)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 66 (bound), 1973-1974 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 47)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 67 (bound), 1974-1975 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 48)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Volume 1, No. 1-12 (new iteration of the paper), 1979 (Item Shelf 36/3F, Volume 49)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Index A-K, undated (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 50)
  - The Polytechnic Reporter, Index L-Z, undated (Item Shelf 36/5E, Volume 51)